Guide to the Dept. of Fiber Science and Apparel Design records, 2007-2018.
Dept. of Fiber Science and Apparel Design records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Fiber Science and Apparel Design records, 2007-2018.
23-19-3780
New York State College of Human Ecology.Dept. of Fiber Science and Apparel Design.
1 cubic feet.
Printed Materials, Publications, Publications, Movie Film, Videotapes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes, posters, brochures, faculty annual reports, publications, and DVD of 2007 design league fashion show.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Formerly the Department of Textiles and Design, in 2007 it changed its name to the Dept. of Fiber Science and Apparel Design.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes, posters, brochures, faculty annual reports, publications, and DVD of 2007 design league fashion show.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology.; New York State College of Human Ecology.Dept. of Textiles and Apparel.
Subjects:
Textile fabrics--Study and teaching.; Textile schools--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Clothing and dress--Study and teaching.; Clothing industry--Study and teaching.; Clothing trade--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
See also Dept. of Textiles and Apparel records #23-19-2807
See also New York State College of Home Economics records #23-2-749
See also New York State College of Human Ecology records #23-2-2817
RELATED MATERIAL
Additional material and digital versions can be found online here: http://ecommons.library.cornell.edu/handle/1813/11737
SERIES LIST
Series I. Events
Series II. Publicity
Series III. Reports
Series IV. Course Material
Series V. Faculty Meeting Minutes
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Events
  - Fashion Show, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Design League Fashion Show DVD, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fiber Society Fall Meeting and Technical Conference - Program, 2016-10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Barbara Kuhlman Scholars' Fiber Arts and Wearable Art Exhibition - Program, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Series II. Publicity
  - Event Posters, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Event Posters and Brochures, 2008-2018 (Box 2)
  - Department Brochures, 2007-2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Event Posters, 1994-2017 (Box 49)
  - Event Poster "Surface Design in Fashion", 2018-01-22-2018-02-08 (Folder 1)
- Series III. Reports
  - Faculty Annual Reports, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    See faculty reports in electronic format in collection #23-2-2817
  - Faculty Annual Reports, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Series IV. Course Material
  - FSAD 314 - Digital Textile Design and Printing, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Master of Arts in Fashion Studies program proposal and letter of intent, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Series V. Faculty Meeting Minutes
  - Meeting Minutes, 2006-2016 (Box 3, Folder 1-10)